<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ace Writing Services</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ace Writing Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2020-2024 Thulite</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:43:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Accessibility Statements</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-importance-of-accessibility-statements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-importance-of-accessibility-statements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-an-accessibility-statement&#34;&gt;What is an accessibility statement?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An accessibility statement is a public document that communicates what an organisation is doing to provide digital products, services, and content that are accessible to disabled people.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the New Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/welcome-to-the-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/welcome-to-the-new-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the new website! Previously, my portfolio and introductory information was hosted on Notion, which, while convenient, did not offer much in the way of customisation or professionalism. With this new site, I can modify it as I wish and it&amp;rsquo;s also connected to Ace Writing Services&amp;rsquo; new domain. Emails can also now be received at &lt;strong&gt;contact@acewritingservices.co.uk&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advertising Policy (Anonymised)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/policy-documents/advertising-policy-anonymised/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/policy-documents/advertising-policy-anonymised/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;effective-date&#34;&gt;Effective Date&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;9 August 2024&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This document has been written by [REDACTED] to communicate to both advertisers and customers our strategy and approach to allowing advertising through services provided by us.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Queries about this Advertising Policy should be directed in the first instance to [REDACTED].&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When referring to a particular part of this Advertising Policy, reference should be made to paragraph numbers (i.e., this is Paragraph 3).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;advertising-guidelines&#34;&gt;Advertising Guidelines&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Any promotion of a particular product or service does not indicate [REDACTED]’s endorsement of said product or service.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[REDACTED] may publish articles and/or newsletters that aim to promote other companies or organisations as part of an established partnership. Such partnerships will be declared unambiguously for our customers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[REDACTED] will not accept any advertising that is intentionally deceptive or malicious or any advertising that may damage our reputation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ads must clearly indicate the advertiser as well as what product or service is being offered.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ad placement is intentional and should always correspond to where it is most appropriate to display a certain ad. Placement should be non-intrusive and not directly affect your experience of using our website.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[REDACTED] will not allow any ads that play audio without your permission.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to our website to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be of interest to you.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;inappropriate-advertising&#34;&gt;Inappropriate Advertising&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;11&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We take all complaints about inappropriate ads extremely seriously in the interest of ensuring our customers are satisfied with their experience with us.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You are encouraged to report inappropriate ads to us so they can be reviewed and subsequently prevented from appearing again. Please include the following information:&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;a screenshot of the ad&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the URL/link to the ad&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;your country&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;your browser&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;your device&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;time of day&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We will usually communicate any decision made about a report of inappropriate advertising as soon as is practicable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;changes-to-this-policy&#34;&gt;Changes to This Policy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;14&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[REDACTED] reserves the right to make additions, amendments or omissions to this Advertising Policy at any time, for any reason, with or without notice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Where significant changes are made, [REDACTED] assures you that it will make every reasonable effort to communicate this to you via email, usually thirty (30) days before changes take effect.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilateral Service Agreement (AstroNode)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/legal-documents/bilateral-service-agreement-astronode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/legal-documents/bilateral-service-agreement-astronode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Service Agreement (the “Agreement”) is entered into by and between the Client and &lt;em&gt;Hiun LLC&lt;/em&gt;, doing business as &lt;em&gt;AstroNode&lt;/em&gt; (referred to hereafter as the “Service Provider”), also referred to collectively as the “Parties”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blurplefied Privacy Policy (Project Blurple)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/legal-documents/blurplefied-privacy-policy-project-blurple/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/legal-documents/blurplefied-privacy-policy-project-blurple/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;document-overview&#34;&gt;Document Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Project Blurple (“we”, “us” or “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of information (i.e. any information relating to an identified or identifiable user) who interact with the Blurplefied Discord bot and use the services available therein (the “Services”). Amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted to the Services and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of the services following the posting of any amendment to this Privacy Policy hereinafter shall constitute your acceptance of aforementioned amendment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countr Privacy Policy (Promise Solutions)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/legal-documents/countr-privacy-policy-promise-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/legal-documents/countr-privacy-policy-promise-solutions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as the clauses herein specify exactly what information we collect about you, how it is used, who has access to it, and how it can be deleted (the right to erasure), as well as any other information we feel you have the right to know.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countr Terms of Service (Promise Solutions)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/legal-documents/countr-terms-of-service-promise-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/legal-documents/countr-terms-of-service-promise-solutions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please read these Terms of Service (these &amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) carefully as they govern your use of Promise Solutions’ (the “Service Provider”) services through Countr (the “Bot”), an application on the Discord platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editorial Policy (Anonymised)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/policy-documents/editorial-policy-anonymised/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/policy-documents/editorial-policy-anonymised/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;effective-date&#34;&gt;Effective Date&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;10 August 2024&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This document has been written by [REDACTED] to document our approach to how articles and newsletters should be approached from an editorial perspective.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Queries about this Editorial Policy should be directed in the first instance to [REDACTED].&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When referring to a particular part of this Editorial Policy, reference should be made to paragraph numbers (i.e., this is Paragraph 3).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-values&#34;&gt;Our Values&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[REDACTED] asserts that it will adhere to the principles of objectivity, impartiality and integrity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Any articles or newsletters published by us will be written in a way that does not intentionally influence the reader’s viewpoint on a topic in one way or another.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Instead, articles and newsletters should communicate multiple viewpoints where possible, and should equally balance arguments where applicable to ensure readers can make their own judgments as appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We recognise the importance of editorial independence - if there is a conflict of interest between a writer and an organisation or individual discussed in an article, this must be disclosed in the public interest and for transparency purposes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;accessibility-commitment&#34;&gt;Accessibility Commitment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;8&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;As part of our mission, we want everyone to be able to access our publications with ease. As such, we promise to use English in a way that can be accessed by as many people as possible. This extends beyond using simple wording where anything more complicated would be unnecessary - it also includes using accessible sentence structures. This also helps with readability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We would like to hear from our readers about any publications that are not accessible - even the small things are important so we can be sure to make improvements to new releases as we continue to develop our brand and voice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;referencing--sources&#34;&gt;Referencing &amp;amp; Sources&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;10&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;While [REDACTED] is not compelled or required by any means to declare our sources of information through referencing or otherwise, we may do so anyway in instances where certain information is specialist in nature or where our writers have made a determination that it is unlikely to be widely known.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We assert that we will thoroughly consider the nature, origin and purpose of any sources and whether information derived from these sources is reliable and fit to be included in one of our publications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;copyright--regulatory-compliance&#34;&gt;Copyright &amp;amp; Regulatory Compliance&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;12&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[REDACTED] is committed to ensuring that any copyrighted materials used in published articles or newsletters are appropriately attributed to their respective owners.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pursuant to the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act 1988 with the legal extent of England and Wales (s.304), fair dealing for criticism, review or quotation is allowed for any type of copyright work&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;However, it is not permitted for photographs. As such, [REDACTED] will seek permission to reproduce photographs where this is possible.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;reporting-breaches&#34;&gt;Reporting Breaches&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;15&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We are committed to protecting our integrity and reputation as a reliable source of information on the topic of aeronautics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Accordingly, if you feel we have fallen short of our editorial standards as set out above, you are welcome and encouraged to contact us at [REDACTED] and we will aim to respond to you within a reasonable timeframe.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In response to any complaints, we will provide a response that details what we have done to rectify the problem if we agree that there has been a breach of this policy, or, in some situations, we will provide reasons to justify our original decision.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;changes-to-this-policy&#34;&gt;Changes to This Policy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;18&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[REDACTED] reserves the right to make additions, amendments or omissions to this Editorial Policy at any time, for any reason, with or without notice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Where significant changes are made, [REDACTED] assures you that it will make every reasonable effort to communicate this to you via email, usually thirty (30) days before changes take effect.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extended Project Qualification Essay Sample</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/personal-writing/extended-project-qualification-essay-sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/portfolio/personal-writing/extended-project-qualification-essay-sample/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;callout callout-note d-flex flex-row mt-4 mb-4 pt-4 pe-4 pb-2 ps-3&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;svg&#xA;  xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34;&#xA;  width=&#34;24&#34;&#xA;  height=&#34;24&#34;&#xA;  viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34;&#xA;  fill=&#34;none&#34;&#xA;  stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34;&#xA;  stroke-width=&#34;2&#34;&#xA;  stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34;&#xA;  stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34;&#xA; &#xA; class=&#34;outline/info-circle svg-inline callout-icon me-2 mb-3&#34; id=&#34;svg-info-circle&#34; role=&#34;img&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;path stroke=&#34;none&#34; d=&#34;M0 0h24v24H0z&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34;/&gt;&#xA;  &lt;path d=&#34;M3 12a9 9 0 1 0 18 0a9 9 0 0 0 -18 0&#34; /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;path d=&#34;M12 9h.01&#34; /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;path d=&#34;M11 12h1v4h1&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;callout-content&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;callout-title&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;        &lt;p&gt;Note&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/information/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:04:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/information/introduction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The portfolio available on this area of the website includes a number of documents produced under contract for clients as to represent my writing ability. Some personal or academic documents may also be included to further exemplify this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
